ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New Jersey, Local #195 and Mr. Stag, Inc., 1974 (Box 140, Folder 32)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Murray Cleaners, Inc., 1985-1990 (Box 140, Folder 33)
- Toronto Joint Board and Murray Uniform, 1986 (Box 140, Folder 34)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Napp's, Inc., 1965-1986 (Box 141, Folder 1)
- Toronto Joint Board and Nash Pant Co., Ltd., 1986 (Box 141, Folder 2)
- Cleveland Joint Board and the M. O'Neil Co., 1978-1984 (Box 141, Folder 3)
- Pacific Northwest Joint Board and Pacific Outfitting Co., 1977-1988 (Box 141, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and Pan Am Mens Wear, 1980-1981 (Box 141, Folder 5)
- Tannery and Leather Workers Union Local #1712 and Pan American Tanning Corp., 1974-1992 (Box 141, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board and Park Kenny Corp., 1984-1988 (Box 141, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Penn State Clothing Corp., 1969-1990 (Box 141, Folder 8)
- New York Joint Board and Persall Tailors, 1975-1977 (Box 141, Folder 9)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #187 and Polo Clothing Co., Inc., 1977-1991 (Box 141, Folder 10)
- New England Regional Joint Board and J&R Pollack, 1966-1989 (Box 141, Folder 11)
- Southern Organizational Department and Pollock Manufacturing, Inc. (Brew Apparel), 1973-1991 (Box 141, Folder 12)
- New York Joint Board and Poppy's Tailors, Inc., 1975 (Box 141, Folder 13)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Prince Gardner, Inc., 1991 (Box 141, Folder 14)
- New York Joint Board and Promenade, Inc., 1981-1984 (Box 141, Folder 15)
- Rochester Joint Board and Proud Winds, Inc., 1977 (Box 141, Folder 16)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Carl Putzer Men's Wear, Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 141, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and Quality Haberdasher, Inc., 1975-1984 (Box 141, Folder 18)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and R & S Pants Co., Inc. (Wyoming Valley Garment), 1956-1991 (Box 141, Folder 19)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Raleigh's Clothiers, Inc., 1962-1989 (Box 141, Folder 20)
- New York Joint Board and Raphael Clothes, Inc., 1981-1984 (Box 141, Folder 21)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Alex Reich Clothes, Inc., 1963-1977 (Box 141, Folder 22)
- General Office and Reltoc Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1972-1990 (Box 141, Folder 23)
  Beaverton, AL
- General Office and Reltoc Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1972-1990 (Box 141, Folder 24)
  Florence, AL
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Reltoc Manufacturing Co., 1970-1992 (Box 141, Folder 25)
  Forrest City, AR
- Southern Regional Joint Board and Reltoc Manufacturing Co., 1966-1986 (Box 141, Folder 26)
  Winfield, AL
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Reltoc Manufacturing Co., 1987-1990 (Box 141, Folder 27)
  Wynne, AR
- New York Joint Board and Richfield 5 Towns, Ltd., 1981-1984 (Box 141, Folder 28)
- New York Joint Board and Richfield Clothes Kings Plaza, 1981-1984 (Box 141, Folder 29)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Risto, Inc., 1979-1991 (Box 141, Folder 30)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Jack Robbins Clothing Co., 1980-1991 (Box 141, Folder 31)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #667A and John Roberts, Inc. (Act II, Inc.), 1983-1993 (Box 142, Folder 1)
- Rochester Joint Board and Rochester Die Cutting and Finishing, Inc. (Rosco Manufacturing), 1970-1988 (Box 142, Folder 2)
- New Jersey, Local #195 and Roger Clothes, Inc., 1972-1980 (Box 142, Folder 3)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Rogoff Brothers, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 4)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Rosenlum's, Inc., 1986 (Box 142, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board and Rosenthal-Maretz Co., Inc., 1975 (Box 142, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Rosey's Tailors, 1992 (Box 142, Folder 7)
- New York Joint Board and Rowma Tailoring, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 142, Folder 8)
- New York Joint Board and Royal Fashion Clothes, Inc., 1981-1984 (Box 142, Folder 9)
- New York-New Jersey Joint Board and Royal Sewing Co., Inc., 1991 (Box 142, Folder 10)
- Cincinnati Joint Board and Rubel's Squire, 1968-1972 (Box 142, Folder 11)
- New York Joint Board and Anthony Rubino, 1977-1982 (Box 142, Folder 12)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and S & S Tailoring, 1980-1991 (Box 142, Folder 13)
- Toronto Joint Board and Sainthill Levine, 1987-1988 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  Production Workers Unit
- Toronto Joint Board and Sainthill Levine, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  Tag End Unit
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Richard Bennett, 1980-1985 (Box 142, Folder 16)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Sanders Cleaning Co., 1990 (Box 142, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and A. Scafati, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 18)
- New York Joint Board and Shaw & Ross, 1978-1988 (Box 142, Folder 19)
- New England Regional Joint Board and Shultzy's Head to Toe Shop, 1974-1993 (Box 142, Folder 20)
- Rochester Joint Board and Somerville Packaging Corp. (Rendoll Operations), 1969-1994 (Box 142, Folder 21)
- Local #158 and Specialty Pants Manufacturing Corp., 1968-1977 (Box 142, Folder 22)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Spoo & Son (Menswear Group), 1980-1983 (Box 142, Folder 23)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and State Manufacturing Co., 1959-1992 (Box 142, Folder 24)
- Southern Organizational Department and Southeastern Textile Shrinkers, 1970-1984 (Box 142, Folder 25)
- Pacific Northwest Joint Board, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #71 and John Stern's, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 26)
- General Office and Oberman Manufacturing Co., 1959-1966 (Box 142, Folder 27)
- New York Joint Board and Strong Uniform Co., Inc., 1975 (Box 142, Folder 28)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Swank Newman Cleaners, 1990 (Box 142, Folder 29)
- New York Joint Board and Tall Men Stores of Brooklyn, Inc., 1981-1984 (Box 142, Folder 30)
- New York Joint Board and Tall Men Stores, Inc., 1981-1988 (Box 142, Folder 31)
- New York Joint Board and Tweed's Mens Wear, 1978-1984 (Box 142, Folder 32)
- Montreal Joint Board and Quebec, Inc., 1984-1989 (Box 142, Folder 33)
- New York Joint Board and Twenty-Five Mens Wear & Empire State Clothes, 1978-1981 (Box 142, Folder 34)
- New York Joint Board and Union Square Clothing Co., Inc., 1990 (Box 142, Folder 35)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and United Tailor, Inc., 1977-1987 (Box 142, Folder 36)
- New York Joint Board and University Tailoring, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 142, Folder 37)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Uptown Shoes, Inc., 1992 (Box 142, Folder 38)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, Local #352 and Wallach's, 1990 (Box 142, Folder 39)
- New York Joint Board and Jerry Ward, Inc., 1975 (Box 142, Folder 40)
- Southern Regional Joint Board and Washington Holding Co., Inc., 1993 (Box 142, Folder 41)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Harry Weinraub, Inc., 1983-1990 (Box 142, Folder 42)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Worth's, 1965-1976 (Box 142, Folder 43)
- California Joint Board, Local #14Z and Xerox Corp., 1986 (Box 142, Folder 44)
- General Office and Yorke Shirt (Julius Simon Ruffalo, Inc.), 1990-1993 (Box 142, Folder 45)
- New York Joint Board and Young Robbins, 1981-1984 (Box 142, Folder 46)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and J.P. Zito, Inc., 1982-1990 (Box 142, Folder 47)
- General Office and Accurate Lace Dye Experts, Inc., 1995 (Box 143, Folder 1)
- Local #1790 and Accurate Lace Dye Experts, Inc., 1944-1993 (Box 143, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and Ajax Shoulder Pad Co., 1968-1980 (Box 143, Folder 3)
- Alabama, Local #2602 and American Apparel, Inc., 1993 (Box 143, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and American Linen Supply Co., 1993-1996 (Box 143, Folder 5)
- Southern Regional Joint Board and American Trouser, Inc., 1994 (Box 143, Folder 6)
- Local #1196T and American White Cross, Inc. (National Patent Medical Partnership), 1991-1994 (Box 143, Folder 7)
- Local #1606 and Amoco Fabrics and Fibers, Ltd., 1993 (Box 143, Folder 8)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Ansell Edmont Industrial, Inc., 1992-1995 (Box 143, Folder 9)
- New York Joint Board and Bari Manufacturing Corp., 1979-1990 (Box 143, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board, Local #250C and #253C and Berkley Cravats, Ltd., 1986 (Box 143, Folder 11)
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Board and Michael Berkowitz Co., Inc., 1991 (Box 143, Folder 12)
- Montreal Joint Board and J.A. Besner & Sons, Ltd., 1978 (Box 143, Folder 13)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Bierner & Son, Inc., 1995 (Box 143, Folder 14)
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union and Bierner & Son, Inc., 1965-1992 (Box 143, Folder 15)
- California Joint Board and Jay Briggs, Inc., 1982 (Box 143, Folder 16)
- Southern California Joint Board and Brooks Brothers, 1968-1977 (Box 143, Folder 17)
- Local #2102 and Buster Brown Apparel, Inc., 1995 (Box 143, Folder 18)
- Local #2102 and Buster Brown Apparel, Inc., 1953-1992 (Box 143, Folder 19)
- Western Regional Joint Board California District and California Ranchwear, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 20)
- Southern California Joint Board and California Ranchwear, 1965-1993 (Box 143, Folder 21)
- Montreal Joint Board and Charell, Ltd., 1977-1990 (Box 143, Folder 22)
- Portland Area Joint Board and Chase Bag Co., 1948-1990 (Box 143, Folder 23)
- New York Joint Board and Cleve-Tenn Industries, Inc., 1979-1990 (Box 143, Folder 24)
- New England Regional Joint Board and Cliftex Corp. (Dartmouth Clothing), 1961-1990 (Box 143, Folder 25)
- Mid-Atlantic Joint Board and Colshire Manufacturing Co., 1991 (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Pacific Northwest Joint Board and Columbia Wool Scouring Mills, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 2)
- Pacific Northwest Joint Board and Columbia Wool Scouring Mills, 1951-1991 (Box 144, Folder 3)
- Local #1790 and College House Manufacturing, 1977-1991 (Box 144, Folder 4)
- Local #1584 and Cone Mills Corp. (Salisbury Plant), 1982-1992 (Box 144, Folder 5)
- Local #1584 and Cone Mills Corp. (Salisbury Plant), 1964-1981 (Box 144, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board and Cooper Sportswear Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1969-1990 (Box 144, Folder 7)
- New York Joint Board and Cortese, Inc., 1994 (Box 144, Folder 8)
- Local #1355 and Cranston Print Works Co., 1994 (Box 144, Folder 9)
- Southern New England Joint Board, Local #1000T and Crown Yarn Dye Co., Inc., 1992 (Box 144, Folder 10)
- Local #1000T and Crown Yarn Dye Co., Inc., 1939-1982 (Box 144, Folder 11)
- Southern Organizational Department and Hallmark Emblems, 1979-1991 (Box 144, Folder 12)
- New York-New Jersey Regional Joint Board, Local #292H and Harris-Tipograph, Inc., 1994 (Box 144, Folder 13)
- New York-New Jersey Joint Board and Harris-Tipograph, Inc., 1983-1991 (Box 144, Folder 14)
- Southwest Region, Local #2575 and Heel Rite Corp., 1992 (Box 144, Folder 15)
- Greater Northeastern Joint Board, Local #39T and Homestead Industries, Inc., 1995 (Box 144, Folder 16)
- New York Joint Board and Ideal Shoulder Pad Co., Inc., 1968-1990 (Box 144, Folder 17)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Illinois Glove Co., 1992 (Box 144, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Immaculate Laundry, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 19)
- New York Joint Board and Imperial Coat Front Co., 1968-1990 (Box 144, Folder 20)
- New Jersey, Local #1932 and Interstate Dyeing and Finishing Co., 1942-1980 (Box 144, Folder 21)
- New York-New Jersey Regional Joint Board, Local #292H and Ira Katz New York Corp., 1994 (Box 145, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board and Irwin Manufacturing Co., Ltd., 1978-1990 (Box 145, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board and Irwin Manufacturing Co., Ltd., 1993 (Box 145, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board and J.A. Besner & Sons, Ltd., 1993 (Box 145, Folder 4)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Johansen Brothers Shoe Co., Inc., 1995 (Box 145, Folder 5)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Kellwood Co., 1979-1991 (Box 145, Folder 6)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Kim Michaels, Inc., 1990-1995 (Box 145, Folder 7)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and LaDonna Sportswear, Inc., 1994 (Box 145, Folder 8)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and LaDonna Sportswear, Inc., 1992 (Box 145, Folder 9)
- New York Joint Board and Leathermark Sportswear Corp., 1975-1985 (Box 145, Folder 10)
- General Office and Lee County Manufacturing (Superior Surgical), 1993-1995 (Box 145, Folder 11)
- Southern Organizational Department and Lee County Manufacturing, 1966-1992 (Box 145, Folder 12)
- New York, General Office and Lilly Industries, Inc., 1952-1993 (Box 145, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Martin Blouse Co., 1994 (Box 145, Folder 14)
- New York-New Jersey Regional Joint Board, Local #292H and Meren Industries, Inc., 1991-1994 (Box 145, Folder 15)
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Local #13 and Meren Industries Corp., 1964-1982 (Box 145, Folder 16)
- New York-New Jersey Regional Joint Board, Local #215 and Mespo Umbrella Co., Inc., 1994 (Box 145, Folder 17)
- General Office and Mespo Umbrella, Ltd., 1941-1991 (Box 145, Folder 18)
- New York Joint Board and Midlantic-New York Pad (Abetta Products), 1968-1990 (Box 145, Folder 19)
- Northern District Joint Board and Milaca Mills, Inc., 1994 (Box 145, Folder 20)
- Hat Workers Union, Local #125 and Miller Brothers, Inc., 1993 (Box 145, Folder 21)
- Hat Workers Union, Local #125 and Miller Brothers, Inc., 1964-1990 (Box 145, Folder 22)
- General Office and Missbrenner Manufacturing, Inc., 1970-1990 (Box 145, Folder 23)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Moderne Gloves, 1967-1994 (Box 145, Folder 24)
- Glove Cities District and Mohawk & Hudson River Humane Society, Inc., 1995 (Box 145, Folder 25)
- General Office and Mohawk & Hudson River Humane Society, Inc., 1980 (Box 145, Folder 26)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board and Monro Prints Plant (Franco Manufacturing), 1993 (Box 145, Folder 27)
- Catawba Valley Joint Board and Monroe Prints, 1978-1990 (Box 145, Folder 28)
- Montreal Joint Board and Montreal Fast Print (1975), Ltd., 1994 (Box 146, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board and Montreal Fast Print (1975), Ltd., 1982-1988 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  French and English
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Local #921 and Monterey Mills, Inc., 1987 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- New York & New Jersey Regional Joint Board, Local #1790 and National Knitted Processors, Inc., 1993 (Box 146, Folder 4)
- Greater New York Joint Board, Local #1790 and National Knitted Processors, Inc., 1977-1990 (Box 146, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board and Niemore Contractors, Inc., 1966-1990 (Box 146, Folder 6)
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Board and Orx Railway Corp., 1993 (Box 146, Folder 7)
- General Office and Outdoor Venture Corp., 1992 (Box 146, Folder 8)
- Quebec Joint Board, Local #2396 and Peerless Carpet Corp., 1992-1995 (Box 146, Folder 9)
- Quebec Joint Board and Peerless Rug, Ltd., 1981-1992 (Box 146, Folder 10)
- Local #1733 and Local #1932 and Perennial Print Corp., 1995 (Box 146, Folder 11)
- Local #1733 and Perennial Print Corp., 1953-1990 (Box 146, Folder 12)
- Buffalo Joint Board and Perfection Pad Co., 1965-1985 (Box 146, Folder 13)
- Greater Toronto Textile Joint Board and Perma Foam, Ltd., 1985-1990 (Box 146, Folder 14)
- Canada, Local #717P and Perma Foam, Ltd., 1994 (Box 146, Folder 15)
- Eastern District Joint Board, Local #1448T and Phoenix Dye Works, 1990-1994 (Box 146, Folder 16)
- Local #1733, Local #1932 and Poughkeepsie Finishing Corp., 1951-1980 (Box 146, Folder 17)
- Local #1733 and Poughkeepsie Finishing Co., 1983-1990 (Box 146, Folder 18)
- Local #7587 and Prima Warping, Inc., 1993 (Box 146, Folder 19)
- Local #1733 and Rainbow Dyeing & Finishing Co., 1969-1990 (Box 146, Folder 20)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #177 and River Falls Manufacturing Co., 1994 (Box 146, Folder 21)
- Local #7587 and River Warping, Inc., 1995 (Box 146, Folder 22)
- Local #7587 and River Warping, Inc., 1950-1990 (Box 146, Folder 23)
- Greater Northeastern Joint Board, Local #1035T and Roselin Manufacturing Co., 1992-1995 (Box 146, Folder 24)
- Montreal Joint Board and L. Salomon & Sons, 1992 (Box 146, Folder 25)
- New York-New Jersey Regional Joint Board, Local #215 and Schertz Umbrella, Inc., 1994 (Box 146, Folder 26)
- New York, Local #215 and Schertz Umbrellas, Inc., 1970-1991 (Box 147, Folder 1)
- California Joint Board and Sierra Plastics Co., 1956-1991 (Box 147, Folder 2)
- Local #829 and Southeastern Textile Shrinkers (Manhattan Sponging Works), 1994 (Box 147, Folder 3)
- General Office and Levi Strauss & Co., 1992 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  Harlingen, TX
- General Office and Levi Strauss & Co., 1992 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  McAllen, TX
- Southern Organizational Department and Levi Strauss & Co., 1957-1991 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  Valdosta, GA
- Montreal Joint Board and Levi Strauss & Co. (Canada), Inc., 1973-1991 (Box 147, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Scranton Export Clothing Co., Inc., 1992 (Box 147, Folder 8)
- Local #1733 and Tavernon Photo Engraving Co., Inc., 1940-1980 (Box 147, Folder 9)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Taylor Clothing, Inc., 1994 (Box 147, Folder 10)
- Local #1733 and Techniplast, Inc., 1973-1992 (Box 147, Folder 11)
- General Office and Texas Apparel Co. (Salant Corp.), 1994 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  Eagle Pass, TX
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Texas Apparel Co. (Salant Corp.), 1983-1989 (Box 147, Folder 13)
- General Office and Texas Apparel Co. (Salant Corp.), 1994 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  Carrizo Springs, TX
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Texas Apparel (Salant Corp) and Texas Miller Products, Inc., 1974-1994 (Box 147, Folder 15)
- New York-New Jersey Joint Board and United Global Distributors, Inc. (United Export Clothing Co.), 1952-1994 (Box 147, Folder 16)
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Board and W.F.R. Ribbon, Inc., 1992 (Box 147, Folder 17)
- Local #1404T and Warwick Dyeing Corp., 1980-1994 (Box 147, Folder 18)
- General Office and Water Valley Manufacturing, Inc., 1994 (Box 147, Folder 19)
- Southern Regional Joint Boat, Central North Carolina District and Whiteville Apparel Corp., 1993 (Box 147, Folder 20)
- Connecticut, Local #110 and A. Wimpfheimer & Bro., Inc., 1937-1992 (Box 147, Folder 21)
- New York-New Jersey Regional Joint Board and Windsor Textile Processing, Inc., 1985-1995 (Box 147, Folder 22)
- Toronto, Local #1813 and Automotive Industries (Paramount Division), 1970-1989 (Box 148, Folder 1)
- New York, Local #1906 and Birdair Structures, Inc., 1973-1989 (Box 148, Folder 2)
- Connecticut, Local #2372T and Brintec Corp. (Brand-Rex Co.), 1975-1987 (Box 148, Folder 3)
- New York, Local #215 and Canvas Specialty Co., Inc., 1941-1988 (Box 148, Folder 4)
- New York-New Jersey Joint Board and Continental Combining Corp., 1971-1991 (Box 148, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Textile Joint Board and Craftex Mills, Inc., 1941-1983 (Box 148, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia, Local #25T and Craftex Mills, Inc., 1990 (Box 148, Folder 7)
- Ontario, Local #1915 and Freudenberg Nonwovens, Inc. (Pellon Chemotextiles, Inc.), 1973-1990 (Box 148, Folder 8)
- Ontario, Local #310 and Greb, Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 148, Folder 9)
- Pennsylvania, Local #9-J and J. Wood, 1985-1989 (Box 148, Folder 10)
- New Jersey, Local #7587 and Ronitex Jacquard Mills, Inc., 1962-1989 (Box 148, Folder 11)
- Chicago, Local #1437 and Johnson & Johnson, 1956-1964 (Box 149, Folder 1)
- Chicago, Local #1437 and Johnson & Johnson, 1966-1982 (Box 149, Folder 2)
- Chicago, Local #1437 and Johnson & Johnson, 1984-1988 (Box 149, Folder 3)
- New England, Local #2445 and W.S. Libbey Co., 1983-1986 (Box 149, Folder 4)
- Ontario, Local #1740 and Newlands Textiles, Inc., 1964-1986 (Box 149, Folder 5)
- Ontario, Local #1740 and Newlands Textiles, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 149, Folder 6)
- New Jersey, Local #7587 and Prima Warping, Inc., 1962-1992 (Box 149, Folder 7)
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Board, Local #2328 and Signode Packaging Systems (Cyklop Strapping Corp.), 1982-1992 (Box 149, Folder 8)
- Central Massachusetts Joint Board and Sudbury River Dye Co., 1974-1989 (Box 149, Folder 9)
- Virginia, Local #1622 and Trego Stone Corp., 1964-1988 (Box 149, Folder 10)
- Granite State Joint Board and Unifirst Corp. (Interstate Industrial Uniform Rental), 1961-1987 (Box 149, Folder 11)
- Greater New York Joint Board and United Cut Products, Inc., 1954-1990 (Box 149, Folder 12)
- Federation of Dyers, Finishers, Printers and Bleachers and United Merchants and Manufacturers, Inc. (Arkwright Finishing Corp.), 1940-1987 (Box 149, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Lustberg Nast & Co., Inc., 1941-1960 (Box 150, Folder 1)
- Sporstwear, Sheep lined & Leather and McGregor Manufacturing Co., 1953 (Box 150, Folder 2)
- Shirt Agreement, Manhattan Shirt Co., 1945 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  Americus, GA
- General Office and Palm Beach Co., 1950 (Box 150, Folder 4)
- Talladega, Roanoke, AL and Palm Beach Co., 1950 (Box 150, Folder 5)
- Knoxville, TN and Palm Beach Co., 1950 (Box 150, Folder 6)
- Kentucky and Palm Beach Co., 1950 (Box 150, Folder 7)
- Blackville, SC and Palm Beach Co., 1950 (Box 150, Folder 8)
- Southeastern Clothing Regional Board and Palm Beach Co., 1960-1962 (Box 150, Folder 9)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Publix Shirt Co., 1933-1960 (Box 150, Folder 10)
- General Office and Rose Bros., Inc., 1943-1947 (Box 150, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Shirts and Savada Bros., Inc., 1949 (Box 150, Folder 12)
- Pennsylvania Shirts and Publix Shirt Corp., 1947 (Box 150, Folder 13)
- New York Shirts and Publix Shirt Corp., 1947 (Box 150, Folder 14)
- General Office and Clothing Manufacturers' Association, 1957-1977 (Box 151, Folder 1)
- General Office and Clothing Manufacturers' Association, 1943-1960 (Box 151, Folder 2)
- Membership Book of New York Clothing Manufacturers' Exchange, Inc., 1946 (Box 151, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and New York Manufacturers' Exchange, Inc., 1941-1957 (Box 151, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and Uniform Manufacturers' Exchange, Inc., 1946-1957 (Box 151, Folder 5)
- Collective Bargaining Agreements, Research Files #21-45, 1940-1960 (Box 151, Folder 6)
- Benefits and Insurance Agreements, 1951-1960 (Box 151, Folder 7)
- Collective Labor Agreements, New York Joint Board, 1937-1957 (Box 151, Folder 8)
- General Office, Local Agreements, 1952-1955 (Box 151, Folder 9)
- New York Joint Board and Greater Clothing Contractors Association, Inc., 1947 (Box 151, Folder 10)
- General Office and Cluett Peabody & Co., 1945-1948 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  Georgia
- General Office and F. Jacobson & Sons, Inc., 1940-1960 (Box 151, Folder 12)
- General Office, Cotton Garment Agreements and F. Jacobson & Sons, Inc., 1945 (Box 151, Folder 13)
- Chicago Joint Board and F.O. Jacobson, 1956-1960 (Box 151, Folder 14)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, Capitol District Joint Board and Lustberg, Nast & Co., Inc., 1953-1959 (Box 151, Folder 15)
- South Jersey Joint Board D-J, 1952-1960 (Box 152, Folder 1)
- South Jersey Joint Board K-L, 1952-1960 (Box 152, Folder 2)
- South Jersey Joint Board M-P, 1952-1960 (Box 152, Folder 3)
- South Jersey Joint Board Q-Z, 1952-1960 (Box 152, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, Market Agreements, 1939-1950 (Box 152, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Philadelphia Clothing Contractors' Association, 1960 (Box 152, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, Uniform Agreements, 1941-1952 (Box 152, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Philadelphia Men's Clothing Contractors' Association, 1939-1957 (Box 152, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board A, 1942-1960 (Box 152, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Joint Board B, 1941-1960 (Box 153, Folder 1)
- Philadelphia Joint Board C-Ci, 1942-1956 (Box 153, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Co-Cr, 1945-1960 (Box 153, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Joint Board D, 1941-1960 (Box 153, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Joint Board E, 1947-1960 (Box 153, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Joint Board F, 1947-1960 (Box 153, Folder 6)
- Baltimore Joint Board D-H, 1947-1960 (Box 154, Folder 1)
- Baltimore Joint Board I-K, 1947-1956 (Box 154, Folder 2)